## SUSAN SAYERS

#### **PROFILE**

As a recent graduate from WIT, with a Masters degree in Arts & Heritage Management, I have undertaken several internships within leading organisations such as South Tipperary Arts Office and Brewery Lane Theatre & Arts Centre. These placements have enabled me to develop not only specific industry experience, but also a valuable and transferable skill set in this fast-paced sector.

### **EXPERIENCE**

# ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT, INLAND FISHERIES IRELAND 2017-PRESENT

Processing tender documents. Writing development projects/funding applications.

General administrative duties including answering email queries and typing.

Producing maps and excel spreadsheets of survey data.

ASSISTANT EVENT COORDINATOR, CLONMEL BUSKING FESTIVAL, CLONMEL TOURISM

2017-PRESENT

Design and maintenance of <a href="www.clonmelbuskingfestival.com">www.clonmelbuskingfestival.com</a>. Planning, organisation, PR and marketing for all events. General administrative, IT and ad-hoc duties. Documenting, filming and film editing for all events.

ARTISTIC LIAISON OFFICER, BREWERY LANE THEATRE & ARTS CENTRE 2013-2014

Designed & developed <a href="www.brewerylanetheatre.com">www.brewerylanetheatre.com</a> & designed app interface on MyTheatre. Set up & maintenance of in-house ticket system. Set design & production for all plays. Organisation of feature events including the Film Club & the Tearoom Sessions. Liaised with exhibiting artists & musicians. PR & Marketing for all events.

General administrative, IT and ad-hoc duties.

## SUSAN SAYERS

# ASSISTANT ARTS OFFICER, SOUTH TIPPERARY ARTS OFFICE 2011-2012

PR, Marketing & compilation of stakeholder feedback reports for all Arts Office events including Bealtaine & Festival Cluain Meala. Providing advice & information on Arts Policy Development, Funding for the Arts & the Developmental Arts Programme to the public & stakeholders. Assisted with installation, sourcing of equipment & insurance for Exhibition, Dig Where You Stand, as part of the Curatorial Residency Programme.

General administrative and ad-hoc duties.

#### **EDUCATION**

WATERFORD INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY

MA IN ARTS & HERITAGE MANAGEMENT

2011-2012

Irish Arts, Heritage & Cultural Studies, Strategic & Financial Management, Cultural Tourism & Public Policy Studies, Professional Development & Research, Festival & Events Management, Employment & Legislative Studies, Public Relations, & Museum & Gallery Studies.

LIMERICK SCHOOL OF ART & DESIGN
BA(HONS) IN FINE ART (SCULPTURE & COMBINED MEDIA)
2006-2010

Art History, Fine Art, Studio Practice, Traditional Making Skills, Contemporary Sculptural Practice, Installation, Photography, Film, Sound and Public Art.

### **SKILLS**

Adobe Certified Associate in Web Authoring using Dreamweaver: 2017

Adobe Certified Associate in Visual Communication using Photoshop: 2016-2017

Adobe Certified Associate in Graphic Design & Illustration in Illustrator: 2015-2016

Manual Handling & Fire Safety: 2014

Training for Enterprise: Start your own business course: 2013-2014

Traditional Irish Craft Making Skills: 2011-2012

TEFL/TESOL: 2010-2011

Disability Awareness Training: 2010

## REFERENCES

Alan Cullagh Sally O'Leary

Head Fisheries Inspector Arts Officer

Inland Fisheries Ireland Tipperary Arts Office

<u>alan.cullagh@fisheriesireland.ie</u> <u>oleary.sally@gmail.com</u>

Simon Molloy

**Event Coordinator** 

Clonmel Busking Festival

simonmolloy123@gmail.com